憨豆特工
Johnny English.
五年前 他是我们最顶尖的特工
Five years ago, he was our top agent.
是啊 在莫桑比克有眼无珠
Yeah. Took his eye off the ball in Mozambique.
非要找他吗？
Does it have to be him?
我们的线人指定他
He's the only one our contact will talk to.
他现在在哪？
So where is he?
你来这里为了忘记你的罪过
You came here to forget your life of shame.
但新生活并不容易 英格力士
But the path you must tread to new life will be not be easy, English.
我们这里目的很简单 强化你的弱点
Our purpose here is simple. To strengthen what is weak.
把软的变硬
Make hard what is soft.
这需要时间
This will take time.
意志主宰身体
Mind must be master of the body.
坚强的意志可以隔离身体的痛苦
Strong mind can separate the body from its suffering.
专注得很好 英格力士
Good concentration, English.
不好意思？烫、烫、烫、烫！
Sorry? Hot! Hot! Hot! Hot!
你不年轻了
You are not young.
但智慧随年龄增长
But with age comes wisdom.
当意志主宰身体的时候
When mind is master of the body,
你会再次成为勇士
you will be warrior once more.
师傅 我的命运是什么？
Master, what is my destiny?
我和高级组织一直有联系
I'm in touch with a higher power.
军情7处要你赶最早的航班飞回伦敦
MI7 wants you on the first flight back to London
师傅 我行吗？
Master, am I ready?
不行
No.
靠窗还是走道？
Window seat or aisle?
稍等 早上好 先生
One moment, please. Good morning, sir.
东芝 英国 情报局
Toshiba British Intelligence.
咨询电子产品请按1
For electronic products press one.
和特工谈话 请按2
To speak to an agent, press two.
当然可以 先生 我可以帮你连接到我们网站吗？
Certainly, sir. Can I redirect you to our website?
WWW.间谍for U...
www.spyingforyou.gov.uk.
东芝 英国 情报局
Toshiba British Intelligence.
早上好 先生 有什么可以帮你吗？
Good morning, sir. Can I help you?
乔尼·英格力士
Johnny English.
珀加索斯 正在等您
Pegasus is expecting you.
看着相机
Look into the camera.
不要笑
Don't smile.
憨豆特工2：重生
潘梅拉 桑顿 军情7处总负责人
Pamela Thornton, Head of Ml?
乔尼·英格力士
Johnny English.
请坐
Have a seat.
你离开有一段时间了 英格力士
You've been away for some time, English.
但你没被遗忘
But you haven't been forgotten.
来吧
Come on.
这里的人经常谈起你在莫桑比克的事迹
People here often talk about your adventures in Mozambique.
自那时以来 军情7处成就了很多
Well, Ml? has come a long way since then
枪 车 沙文主义 都灭亡了
The guns, the fast cars, and the chauvinism are all on their way out.
坦白说 我不想你回来
Frankly, I didn't want to see you back.
你是我来这想要改变的
You are everything I came into this service to change.
但我没办法
But my hands are tied.
有时候人们得反对自己
And there are times when one has to go against one's better judgement.
我们有情况
We have a situation.
确实
Indeed.
这只乖猫咪 这只乖猫咪
There's a good puss. There's a good puss.
谁是乖猫咪？谁是乖猫咪？
There's a good pussy. Who's a good pussy?
- 我很惊讶 - 谁是乖猫咪？
- I'm impressed. - Who's a good pussy?
菲尔比从来不让陌生人抱它
Philby never lets strangers pick him up.
我和动物一向都很合得来
I'm very much atone with the animal kingdom.
这只乖猫咪 我知道 谁最可爱？
There's a good puss. I know, I know. Who's lovely? Who's lovely?
乖...
Who...
我们都很乖
We're all lovely.
凯特·萨姆纳 行为心理学家
Kate Sumner, our behavioural psychologist.
久仰大名
I've heard a great deal about you.
事迹辉煌吧
Glowing reports, I trust.
萨姆纳女士告诉我
Tell me, Ms Sumner,
行为心理学家是干嘛...的？
what exactly does a behavioural psychologist do?
透过行为参透心理
Monitor observable behaviour for signs of internal psychology.
就是读人
We read people.
好吧 我们必须找个时间聚聚
Well, we must get together sometime.
你会发现我是一本引人入胜的书
I think you'll find me a real page-turner.
啊
Ah.
珀加索斯 情况是...
So, Pegasus, this situation.
前中央情报局特工提图斯·费舍尔在香港联络我们
Ex-CIA agent Titus Fisher has contacted us from Hong Kong.
他得到一个暗杀中国总理的秘密情报
He has intelligence of a plot to assassinate the Chinese Premier
在下周的盎格鲁-中国会谈
at the Anglo-Chinese talks next week.
我们要你去找到他看有什么信息
We need you to go and find out what he's got.
这样的话 珀加索斯 算我一个
Well, in that case, Pegasus, count me in.
1号特工会在楼下见你
Agent One will meet you downstairs.
然后 我就爬上墙壁 把整个地方炸飞
So, I just scaled the walls, blew the whole place to kingdom come.
一小时后 我就在酒吧里喝白酒
An hour later I'm sitting in the bar with a White Russian in my hand.
跟你说 非常不错
Who was very lovely, too, I can tell you.
西蒙
Simon.
你好 乔尼
Hello, Johnny!
西蒙
Simon,
你看起来棒极了 一如既往
you look wonderful. But, then, you always did.
欢迎归来 你走了多久了？
Welcome back. How long has it been?
不清楚 5年3个月零6天吧
I don't know. Five years, three months and six days, or something.
是啊 莫桑比克
Of course, Mozambique.
那真是让人郁闷的一团乱麻啊
That was a balls-up with a cherry on top.
来吧 帮你整理下
Come on, let's get you sorted.
欢迎来到玩具柜
Welcome to the toy cupboard.
我不会给你手机号的
I won't leave you my number.
你还记得 佩奇吧
You know Patch.
佩奇 库尔特曼 本人
Patch Quartermain, the man himself.
英格力士
English.
不用起
Please, don't get up.
想起也起不来啊
No chance of that.
在测试B-6爆炸鞋的时候炸掉的
Lost them testing the B-6 exploding brogues.
哦 很抱歉 你怎么样？
Oh, I'm so sorry. How are you?
得用这个手了
Have to be this one, I'm afraid.
研究D-10门铃的时候没的
Lost this to the D-10 doorbell.
啊... 还能见到你剩下的部分非常高兴
Ah. Well, it's great to see what's left of you
这个很不错的 最高时速60英里
This is rather good fun, actually. Top speed of 60 mph,
而且我还装上了厉害的东东
and I've managed to add the odd thing.
这边走 我很忙的
This way. I haven't got all day.
不要
Don't!
不要乱动了 好不好？英格力士？
Would you stop meddling, English?
就在这了
Here she is.
啊 劳斯莱斯 幻影
Ah, the Rolls-Royce Phantom.
真正的劳斯莱斯车
Truly the Rolls-Royce of automobiles.
装甲电镀 花里胡哨 说"引擎盖"
Armour plating, all the bells and whistles. Say "Bonnet."
- 引擎盖 - 命令收到
- Bonnet. - Command accepted.
只针对你的语音激活程序
Voice activation recognises only you.
劳斯莱斯已安装他们最新的实验发动机
Rolls has fitted one of their experimental engines.
9升的V16引擎 跑起来像风一样
The nine-litre V16. Goes like the wind.
而且更安静
Only quieter.
棒极了
Beautiful.
跟着
Keep up!
这些是你去香港要带上的
Here's what you'll be taking to Hong Kong.
- 啊 是啊 - 卫星接收机
- Ah, yes. - A satellite receiver,
跟踪装置 塞姆汀口香糖炸药
tracking device, Semtex chewing gum.
我刚刚说啥了？
Now, what did I just say?
那是最新的P-2数字飞镖枪
That's the new P-two digital dart gun.
先生们 提醒一下
Gentlemen. May I remind you all that
目前军情7处的武器就是谈判
MI7's current weapon of choice is dialogue?
我们喜欢你生气的时候 珀加索斯
We do love it when you get strict, Pegasus.
英格力士 你今晚去香港
English, you go to Hong Kong tonight.
费舍尔会和你联系
Fisher will contact you there.
为了确保接头规范
To ensure protocol is observed,
我派人和你一起去
I'm sending someone with you.
塔克特工
Agent Tucker.
非常荣幸 先生
It will be an honour, sir.
有人拎包不错
Well, it'll be good to have somebody to carry the bags.
你在特勤局外闹出的笑话已经够多了 英格力士
You made a laughing stock out of this service once, English.
在我手下不要 清楚了吗？
Not on my watch. Clear'?
非常清楚 珀加索斯
Crystal clear, Pegasus.
和以前一样 是吧 乔尼？
Just like old times, eh, Johnny?
我要去瑞士 回见了
I'm off to Switzerland. Let's catch up when you get back.
非常好 西蒙
There's nothing I'd like more, Simon.
有人看到变声旅游含片了吗？
Has anyone seen the voice-changing travel lozenges?
嗯...
Um...
没有 没有
No. No.
走吧 塔克
Come on, Tucker.
我到9月才21岁呢 我不应该进来
I'm not 21 till September, sir. I'm not really allowed in.
塔克 你是为女王陛下秘密服务的特工
Tucker, you're an agent working for Her Majesty's Secret Service.
按我说的行事就好
Just act the part.
一万元赌注 谢谢 亲爱的
Ten thousand dollars' worth, please, my lovely.
谢谢
Thank you.
收据 谢谢
And a receipt, please.
塔克 注意线人
Be alert for contact, Tucker.
我们找的是一个戴眼镜的中国男子
We're looking for a Chinese man in spectacles.
先生 还要一杯吗？
Would you like another drink, sir?
先生 戴眼镜的中国人
Sir, the Chinese man in spectacles.
- 不要啤酒了 - 没赌注了
- One more beer. - No more bets, please.
线人
Contact.
晚上好
Evening.
你奶奶病了
Your grandmother is sick.
什么？
What?
你奶奶病了
Your grandmother is sick.
她早死了 当然有病
Well, she's dead. That's how sick she is.
长官 他死了吗？
Is he dead, sir?
是的
Yes.
- 嗨 妈妈 - 出了什么事？
- Hi, Mum. - What's the matter?
不 不 不 不 没问题 没有
No, no, no, no. Nothing's the matter, no.
昨晚有点可笑 但现在没事了
I felt a bit funny last night, but I'm okay now.
你有什么消息？
So, what have you got for us?
在背后密谋刺杀中国总理向平的人物
The people behind the plot to kill Xiang Ping, the Chinese Premier.
其组织叫旋风
A group called Vortex.
从没有听过
Never heard of them.
这里最好的雇佣杀手
Paid assassins. The best there is.
费舍尔 我要名字 证据
Come on, Fisher, I need names, I need evidence!
旋风有个秘密武器
Vortex has a secret weapon.
这是三个钥匙之一
This is one of three keys that,
一起用的时候才可以使用
when used together, gain access to it.
没有这个 旋风就完了
Without this, Vortex is finished
你怎么搞到它的？
How did you get hold of it?
这是我的
It's mine.
什么？
I beg your pardon?
旋风是我们三人
Vortex is three of us.
别来了 费舍尔
Come off it, Fisher
您是雇用杀手？你枪法烂得要死
You, a hired assassin? You couldn't hit a barn door with a banana
关于旋风
And as for Vortex,
明显是洗衣粉的名字 你瞎掰的
clearly you got the name off a box of washing powder.
旋风曾参与莫桑比克事件
Vortex was in Mozambique.
什么？
What?
是吗？真的？
Yeah? Really?
妈妈？妈妈 妈妈 我要走了 要走了
Mum? Mum, Mum, I gotta go. Gotta go.
我们那天都在那 乔尼
We were all there that day, Johnny-boy.
- 对不起 先生 - 什么？
- Excuse me. Sir! - What?
长官 有...
Sir, there's a...
快 快走 快走
Quick, come on! Come on!
女士 让我来帮你
Madam, let me help you with that.
好了 你应该离开这里
Here. Yes, I think you should vacate the area.
这里有很多危险人物
There are some very dangerous people about.
好了
There we go.
追上她 塔克 追上她
Get after her, Tucker, get after her!
什么？
What?
长官 长官
Sir! Sir!
在这 塔克
Over here, Tucker!
跟丢了 长官
I lost her, sir.
看我找到了什么
Look what I found.
这里 长官 这里
This way, sir! This way!
你去街上 我上屋顶
You get down to the street. I'll take the roof.
你不做年轻 但智慧随着年龄增长
You are not young. But with age comes wisdom.
拿过来 黑猩猩
Hand it over, chimp.
来吧 塔克
Come on, Tucker.
我能帮什么吗？
Can I help?
我以女皇陛下的名义征用这艘船
I am commandeering this vessel in the name of Her Majesty.
没问题 中校
Right-0, Wing Commander.
多令人兴奋啊
How exciting!
您在抓什么？要喝点什么吗？
Now, what's your poison? Can I get you something?
有伏特加 朗姆酒
We've got vodka, rum.
我们的首要任务是保证你们的安全
Your safety is our priority.
但你们也可以看看这本册子来帮助我们
But you can help us by familiarizing yourself with this leaflet.
薄荷酒 还剩一点 就这么多了
Cr?e de menthe, a smidgen of port, and that's about it, I'm afraid.
我叫雪莉
I'm Shirley.
你好 雪莉
Hello, Shirley.
头往左边偏点 雪莉 谢谢
Just a tad to your left, Shirley. Thank you.
太棒了 中校
I say, Wing Commander!
- 干得好 长官 干得好 - 就像角斗士一样
- Well played, sir! Well played! - Just like a gladiator!
来吧 放手来吧
Come on. Put 'em up.
干得好 长官 干得好
Well played, sir! Well played!
再来一点香槟 亲爱的
More champagne, my lovely.
没问题 先生
Certainly, sir.
塔克 你确定不要香帝酒或者别的什么？
Tucker' are you sure you don't want a Shandy or something?
我得完成这个任务总结 长官
I have got to finish this mission report, sir.
珀加索斯希望我们一下飞机马上去见她
And Pegasus wants to see us as soon as we touchdown.
任务总结？
The mission report?
哦 来吧 塔克 一点点
Oh, come on, Tucker. Live a little.
你应该学会享受成功
You should learn to savour success.
努力工作
Work hard,
更努力的玩 是吧...
play hard. Isn't that right...
芭芭拉？
Barbara?
旋风完了
Vortex is finished
但更好的是
But better still,
多年来 我一直以为莫桑比克的事是我的错
for years I believed what happened in Mozambique was my fault.
现在我知道只是部分而已
Now I realise it was only partly my fault.
在莫桑比克到底发生什么了？
What did happen in Mozambique?
对不起 先生 我们要着陆了
Excuse me, sir. We're coming in to land.
要我帮您保存那个盒子吗？
Can I stow that overhead for you?
当然
Certainly.
长官 我不认为他叫"苏珊"
Sir, I don't think he's a "Susan."
你又不是语言学家 塔克？
But then you're not a linguist, are you, Tucker'?
不是"苏珊" 是"舒山"
It's not "Susan," it's "Shoooshan."
没记错的话 来自忻州地区
From the Xinzhou region, unless I'm very much mistaken.
谢谢你 舒山
Thank you, Shoooshan.
外相
Foreign Secretary.
希望你得到我们要的东西了 英格力士
I hope you've got something for us, English.
首相非常关注
The Prime Minister is extremely concerned.
当然
He has every reason to be so.
有一个暗杀中国国务院总理的阴谋
There is a plot to kill the Chinese Premier.
由一组叫旋风的无情刺客执行
Masterminded by a group of ruthless assassins called Vortex.
天呐
Good Lord.
但危险已经解除了
The danger, however, has been averted.
现在我们有了这个
Now that we have this.
- 英格力士？- 我知道你要说什么
- English? - Now, I know what you're going to say,
这个东西非常小
it's a pretty small object
但往往小玩意能决定大局
Well, it's often the little things that pack the biggest punch.
- 毕竟 大卫用鹅卵石杀死歌利亚巨人 - 长官
- After all, David killed Goliath with a pebble. - Sir.
拥有这把钥匙 强大的旋风就已经毁灭
The mighty Vortex has been slain by my possession of this small key.
舒山
Shoooshan.
苏珊
Susan.
我们拿到了 但费舍尔招了
We got it, but Fisher talked.
理解 我们会搞定英格力士的
Understood. We'll deal with English.
你又有些清洁工作要做
You've got some more cleaning to do.
妈妈 妈妈 大黄先生来了
Mummy, Mummy! Mr Rhubarb's here!
伊莎 亲爱的 你先带他去娱乐厅吧？
Izzie, darling, why don't you show him into the conservatory?
我马上过去
I'll be with you in just a minute.
好的 来吧 来吧 我们走
Okay. Come on, come on, let's go!
- 走吧？- 快点 大黄先生
- Shall we? - Hurry up, Mr Rhubarb
找到钥匙了再打电话给我
Perhaps when you've found your key, you'll give me a call.
很抱歉 外长 我以为有更好的消息
I'm very sorry, Foreign Secretary. I had hoped to have more for you.
噢 天呐
Oh, God.
珀加索斯 我抓到她了
Pegasus! I've got her!
来吧 你这巫婆
Come on, you witch.
英格力士？
English?
在香港见过她 她是杀手
She was in Hong Kong! She's the killer!
她是我妈妈
She's my mother!
你妈妈是杀手？
Couldn't she be both?
妈妈 妈妈 你没事吧？
Mummy, Mummy, are you all right?
我给你沏杯茶
Let me get you a cup of tea.
- 没事的 妈妈 - 那个男人是谁？
- You'll be fine, Mummy. - Who was that man?
是啊 一杯茶就够了
Yeah, I think a cup of tea, that's what's required.
珀加索斯 我真的非常 非常抱歉
Pegasus, I am truly, truly sorry.
不要向我道歉 向她道歉
Don't apologise to me. Apologise to her.
我知道怎么道歉都于事无补 珀加索斯女士
I cannot apologise enough, Mrs Pegasus.
看错人而已
It was a simple case of mistaken identity, I'm afraid.
你现在很不高兴 我完全理解
Now, I completely understand
但我希望也许...
how upset you are, but I was hoping perhaps...
长官
Sir!
塔克 是她 来自香港的杀手
Tucker! That's her! It's the killer from Hong Kong!
- 不 不是 长官 - 是 这次真的是
- No, it's not her, sir. - It is! This time it's really her!
- 不是她 长官 - 是的 她是
- It's not her, sir! - Yes, it is!
让路
Make way!
长官
Sir.
你这个杀人老太婆
You murderous crone!
奶奶 他在干什么？
Granny! What's he doing?
死吧 死吧
Take that! And that!
嘿 住手
Hey! Stop it.
英格力士
English!
这次我抓到她了 珀加索斯
I've got her this time, Pegasus!
这就是替旋风杀人的那个老巫婆
This is the witch who works for Vortex!
还想来吗？你这个老巫婆？
Want any more' you old hag?
- 英格力士 - 奶奶
- English! - Granny!
你在外长前侮辱我
You humiliate me in front of the Foreign Secretary,
你丢掉关于旋风的唯一线索
you lose our only lead on Vortex,
然后你还想杀死我母亲！
and then you try and kill my mother!
两次
Twice!
珀加索斯 我们还有一个线索
Pegasus, we have another lead.
旋风参与莫桑比克事件！
Vortex was in Mozambique!
他们与昌巴尔总统被杀有关
They were responsible for the death of President Chambal!
不 你才是昌巴尔总统被杀的罪魁祸首
No! You were responsible for the death of President Chambal.
大黄先生赚钱赚得不容易啊
Well, you certainly gave Mr Rhubarb a run for his money.
至少我们知道旋风和莫桑比克的事有关
Still, at least we know Vortex was in Mozambique.
你和珀加索斯说的时候
When you told Pegasus,
四项指标都显示你说的是实话
you displayed all four indicators of someone telling the truth.
这是个面部动作识别系统
This is a facial action coding system.
它的高速摄像机记录肉眼看不见的
Its high-speed cameras record microexpressions,
每个微小动作
invisible to the naked eye.
它可以检测我们所说的情感泄漏
It detects what we call emotional leakage.
萨姆纳女士 我是个训练有素的特工 我不会泄露的
Ms Sumner, I'm a trained agent. I don't "leak."
我要带你回到莫桑比克
I want to take you back to Mozambique.
有必要吗？
Is that really necessary?
看看吧
Take a look at this.
我要带你回莫桑比克
I want to take you back to Mozambique.
看吧
There.
这个可以叫泄漏吗？
Could we call that leakage?
现在 开始吧 我冒着风险下班后留在这
Now, play ball. I'm taking a risk being here after hours.
如果旋风在莫桑比克 也许你看到些什么
If Vortex was in Mozambique, perhaps you saw something.
我要用催眠带你回到那
I'm going to take you back there using hypnosis.
哦 算了吧 不要搞啥新时代巫术
Oh, please. Spare me the new age mumbo jumbo.
英格力士先生 请尊重我的专业
Mr English' please. I'm a professional.
我不打算响下手指
I'm not going to just snap my fingers
就让你说想到的第一件事
and make you say the first thing that comes into your head.
柔软的枕头
Plump pillows.
什么？
Excuse me?
聪明的头脑 美丽的面孔
Brilliant mind. Beautiful face.
难以置信
Incredible.
我完全应付不来
And completely out of my league.
嗯
Mmm.
我要带你回莫桑比克
I'd like to take you back to Mozambique.
告诉我发生了什么 乔尼 你在哪？
Tell me what's happening, Johnny. Where are you?
昌巴尔总统就职当天
President Chambal's inauguration day.
是的 你负责安全
Yes, you're head of security.
一切都很完美
Everything's going perfectly.
今天我们上来了
Today we climb the mountain!
英格力士探员
Agent English.
人们能发言了 很明确
The people have spoken, and the message is clear.
一个和平与繁荣的的未来
A future of peace and prosperity!
备用电源被切断了
The backup electrical supply has been cut.
不 没有 只是被关了
No, it hasn't. It's been turned off.
你知道怎么打开吗？
Do you know how to turn it on?
我要回去了
I should be getting back.
这样的工作非常难
Well, operations like this are always difficult.
但结束后将会非常令人满意
But it's very satisfying when you get a result.
总统相当的安全
The President couldn't be in safer hands.
未来属于莫桑比克
The future belongs to Mozambique!
谢谢
Thank you.
烟花已经开始了
The fireworks have begun.
自由和庆祝的声音
The sound of freedom and celebration.
冷静 乔尼 冷静 回去
Easy, Johnny. Easy. Go back.
在按摩浴池之前 你看到了什么？
Before the Jacuzzi, what did you see?
是的
Yes.
费舍尔
Fisher.
在露台与其他两个
On the terrace with two others.
是的 旋风的三名成员那一天都在
Yes. All three members of Vortex were there that day.
你看到谁了？你看到谁了？乔尼
Who can you see? Who can you see, Johnny?
阿特姆 卡林科
Artem Karlenko.
阿特姆 卡林科 双重间谍
Artem Karlenko, double agent.
军情7处在莫斯科招募的特工
Recruited by MI7 in Moscow.
在他不断杀死威胁他身份的人之后退役
Retired after his penchant for killing people threatened his cover.
五年前 他以谢尔盖 普多夫金的身份
Five years ago, he turned up here
在这里出现
as Sergei Pudovkin.
富有 非常富有
Rich, very rich.
橡树林高尔夫俱乐部成员
A member of the exclusive Oakwood Golf Club,
你将在那里见他
which is where you'll be meeting him.
他在比一场循环赛 长官
He's in a match play competition, sir.
我让你成为他的对手
I'm making you his opponent for the day.
好了 长官 你现在是彼得 亚当斯先生
Done it, sir. You're booked in as Mr Peter Adams.
谢谢 塔克
Thank you, Tucker.
如果卡林科是旋风成员 我要你活着带他回来
If Karlenko is Vortex, I want you to bring him in. Alive.
普斯金先生？
Mr Pussykin?
普多夫金 你应该是
Pudovkin. And you must be Mr
嗯...
Um...
亚当斯先生
Adams.
不错的车 亚当斯先生
Beautiful car, Mr Adams.
啊 劳斯莱斯
Ah, the Royce.
就绪 长官
Ready, sir.
谢谢
Thank you.
我们走吧？
Shall we?
走吧
Let's go.
收到
Command accepted.
亚当斯先生 你从事什么业务？
So, what line of business are you in, Mr Adams?
普多夫金
Pudovkin.
对不起 我是亚当斯先生 你是...
Sorry. Yes, I'm Mr Adams, and you're Mr...
就是你说那个
Whoever you said you were
- 嗯... - 停
- Well... - Stop!
对不起 我以为忘了什么
Sorry, I thought I had forgotten something.
手套 长官？
Glove, sir'?
我可能不是很懂高尔夫 塔克
I may not know much about golf, Tucker,
但我知道怎么握球杆
but I know how to hold the bat.
命中 长官
Shot, sir.
你从事什么行当 普迪金先生？
So, what line of business are you in, Mr Puddykin?
我做清理业务
I made my money in the removals business.
我的一个朋友也从事清理业务 提图斯·费舍尔
A friend of mine had shares in a removals business. Titus Fisher.
你有没有遇到他呢？
You haven't come across him at all?
提醒你下 亚当斯先生 不要踏入深渊
I warn you, Mr Adams, not to stray into the rough.
进得去 出不来
You get in there, you might never come out.
我会牢记的 普迪金先生
I'll bear that in mind, Mr Puddykin.
是普多夫金
Pudovkin. Please.
中
Shot!
我的朋友费舍尔 实际上
As was my friend Fisher, actually.
是在幕后
In the back.
他的清洁工
By his cleaner, of all people.
并没有得到太多
But they didn't take much.
就一个钥匙而已
Just a key
冲一下 从左到右
Break, left to right, I think.
谢谢
Thank you.
树那边
In the trees.
走
Come on.
- 哦 天呐 - 他不能死 他一定不能死
- Oh, my God. - He can't die. He mustn't die.
带他离开这 快 快
Let's get him out of here. Come on! Come on.
他看起来不好 长官
He's not looking good, sir.
我们会带你去看医生 你会没事的
We're getting you to a doctor. You'll be fine.
你知道怎么飞这个 长官？
You do know how to fly these, sir?
- 基本训练的一部分 - 好
- It was part of basic training. - Good.
就像骑自行车
It's just like riding a bike.
好了 都记起来了
Yes. It's all coming back to me.
这是高尔夫酒店祖鲁祖鲁探戈直升机
This is helicopter Golf Hotel Zulu Zulu Tango.
我们机上有伤员
We have a casualty on board.
请求引导到最近医院
Request guidance to nearest hospital.
请通告您的确切位置？
Where's your exact location?
我们的位置？地点？
Our location? Location?
她打坏了我们的导航系统 稍等
She shot out the navigation system. Hang on.
- 兰什多克 - 我们的位置是兰什多克
- Runstock. - Our location is Runstock.
你的高度呢？
What is your altitude?
我们的高度是？
What's our altitude?
约18英寸
About 18 inches.
喂？喂？
Hello? Hello?
对不起 马上走
Sorry. I'll just move.
现在怎么办 长官？
What now, sir'?
我们沿着路走 走1328公路
We'll have to stick to the road. Let's follow the 1328.
在丁汉姆肯定有很多医院
There's bound to be a hospital in Dingham.
看着他 塔克 看着他
Look after him, Tucker. Look after him.
- 他要死了 长官 - 不能让他死 塔克
- I think we're losing him, sir. - We can't lose him, Tucker.
他是我们唯一的线索 想想其他办法
He's our only lead. Try something else.
不要放弃我们 宝贝
Don't give up on us, baby
上帝知道我们已经走到了这一步
Lord knows we've come this far
我们是天使和梦想家
We are The angel and the dreamer
不要放弃我们
Don'! give up on us, I know
我们还能脱险
We could still come through
看 长官 跟着救护车
Look, sir! Follow that ambulance!
好主意
Good idea.
长官 长官 快
Sir. Sir, quickly.
卡林克 卡林克
Karlenko. Karlenko!
第二把钥匙
The second key.
旋风是克格勃...
Vortex is KGB...
- 是的 - 中央情报局
- Yes. - CIA.
还有呢？还有呢？
Yes? Yes?
军情7处
MI7.
难以置信 军情7处有只田鼠
Unbelievable. A vole in MI7.
是内鬼 长官
A mole, sir.
什么？
What?
军情7处有个内鬼
There's a mole in MI7.
有内鬼和田鼠？
There's a mole and a vole?
不 长官 是有内鬼 而不是田鼠
No, sir. There's a mole, not a vole.
我不同意 肯定有只田鼠
Well, I disagree. There's certainly a vole.
我们只知道这么多
I mean, we know that much.
但你说可能也有内鬼
But what you're saying is there might be a mole as well.
珀加索斯
Pegasus.
在军情7处和首相有会
There's a meeting at MI7 with the Prime Minister.
（军情7处总部 1012房间 17:45）
再一次 眼睛向下往左 表示异议
And here again, eyes down and to the left, indicating dissent.
向平都表现在眼睛上了
With Xiang Ping, it's all about the eyes.
谢谢 萨姆纳女士
Thank you, Ms Sumner.
如果会谈继续
If the talks go ahead,
我想你也参与
I'd like you with us.
是的 首相
Yes, Prime Minister.
晚上好 先生们
Good evening, gentlemen.
- 英国探员 - 萨姆纳小姐
- Mr English. - Ms Sumner.
好了
Right.
首相什么时候荣幸光临？
So when is the Prime Minister going to grace us with his presence?
我就是首相
I'm the Prime Minister.
是啊 想得美
Yeah, you wish.
好了 我们都在这
All right. So we're all here.
与中方的会谈极为重要
These talks with China are of paramount importance.
板岩团伙在东南亚
Rogue slates in Southeast Asia
已经开始秘密发展核武器
have begun secretly to develop nuclear weapons.
中方和我们站在一边非常关键
It is vital that we get China onside.
传统习惯上 中方对我们毫不关心
Traditionally, China has been impervious to our concerns,
但我相信向平有机会
but I believe Xiang Ping, given the opportunity,
帮助化解这种局面
can and will help defuse this situation.
他的亲西方立场
Well, with his pro-West stance,
确实提供了一个机会
it certainly offers an opportunity,
但谈判无法继续进行
but the talks can't go ahead
除非我们能保证他的安全
unless we can guarantee his safety.
我相信 我们能做到完善的安全防卫
I believe, with the correct security, that we can.
但如果旋风组织行动的话 就太危险了
If Vortex is operational it's just too dangerous
我同意 首相
I'm inclined to agree, Prime Minister.
还有一个办法
There is a way.
瑞士愿意提供乐堡垒给我们
The Swiss are willing to lend us Le Bastion.
那是他们政府在阿尔卑斯山的要塞
That's their government fortress in the Alps.
那是高海拔建筑工程的极好例子
It's a stunning example of architectural engineering at altitude,
完全固若金汤
and completely impregnable.
那应该能解决我们的安保问题
I mean, that should solve all our security issues.
让会谈继续
Then the talks go ahead.
珀加索斯 我希望你练熟了普通话
Pamela, I hope you've brushed up on your Mandarin.
我希望你跟我在房间里
I'd like you in the room with me,
你最优秀的特工负责安保
and your best man on security.
是的 长官
Yes, Prime Minister.
关于旋风我们有什么消息？
Where are we on Vortex?
英格力士？
English?
旋风包括三个人 费希尔和卡林科
Vortex is three men. Fisher was one, Karlenko was another.
在第三个人的命令下 卡林科今天被杀
Karlenko was killed today on the orders of the third.
有什么线索？
Any leads?
有 但我需要时间
Yes, but I need time.
我们没有时间了
We do not have time.
我们需要知道旋风第三人的身份
We need to know the identity of the third person in Vortex.
给我24个小时
Give me 24 hours.
再来一瓶霍曼尼 康帝？
Another bottle of Romaine-Conti?
- 没问题 - 要什么甜点吗？
Of course. And would you like to choose dessert?
要你
Yes. You.
两把调羹
And bring two spoons.
- 干杯 - 干杯
- Cheers. - Cheers.
干杯
Cheers.
说吧 乔尼 你要问我什么？
So, come on, Johnny, what was it you wanted to ask me'?
西蒙 你知不知道这是什么？
Simon, do you know what this is?
钥匙？
Some sort of key?
卡林科和费舍尔都有一把
Karlenko and Fisher both had one,
他们都因此而死
and they were both killed for them.
好吧 我给实验室的人看看...
Well, I'll give it to the boys at the lab and see...
卡林科告诉我 旋风第三人在军情7处里
Karlenko told me that the third man in Vortex is in MI7.
你相信他？
And you believed him?
西蒙 我要问你一个问题 面对面
Simon, I have to ask you a question, face to face.
你认为可能是谁？
Do you have any idea who it might be?
乔尼 我以为你要说是我
Johnny, I thought you were about to accuse me.
不 老实说
No! I mean, honestly.
- 什么？- 西蒙 安布罗斯 邪恶策划者！
- What? - Simon Ambrose, the evil mastermind!
- 别闹了 - 在我们中间的叛徒！
- Don't. Stop it- - The traitor in our midst!
你！你！
You! You!
西蒙 你是太有趣了
Simon, you are so funny.
笑死了
Hysterical.
哦 亲爱的
Oh, dear.
西蒙 失陪一下好吗？
Would you excuse me for one moment, Simon?
- 长官 - 塔克 不能等等吗？
- Sir. - Tucker, can'! this wait?
长官 是安布罗斯
Sir, it's Ambrose.
是的 我知道是安布罗斯 我和他共进晚餐呢
Yes, I know it's Ambrose. I'm having dinner with him.
不 他是旋风第三人
No, he's the third man in Vortex.
西蒙 安布罗斯？
Simon Ambrose?
他上的伊顿公学
He went to Eton.
西蒙
Simon.
不要动
Leave it.
- 你在... - 退后
- What are you... - Move.
- 好吧 好吧 - 快 退后
- All right, all right. - Come on, move.
塔克
Tucker.
- 你说你不认识卡林科 - 是的
- You said you never knew Karlenko. - That's right.
那你怎么解释这些？
Then how do you explain these?
我侵入卡林科的电脑
I hacked into Karlenko's computer.
这是你和他在莫桑比克吧？
You and him in Mozambique?
有时我也有这种问题 老伙计
Sometimes I have trouble myself, old boy.
你是旋风成员 你是旋风第三人
You're Vortex! You're the third man in Vortex!
塔克 太荒谬了
Tucker, this is ridiculous.
不好意思 稍等一下
Sorry, I'll be with you in just a tick.
是的 我当时在莫桑比克
It's true, I was in Mozambique.
什么？
What?
我在那是因为佩奇 库尔特曼
I was there because of Patch Quartermain.
佩奇？对不起 一秒钟
Patch? Sorry, I'll just be one second.
他是你们要找的人
He's the man you're after.
- 你唬人 - 对不起
- You're bluffing! - Sorry.
我为军情7处里专门设立的一个秘密组织工作
I work for a secret organisation inside MI7
为了把他抓起来
set up specifically to bring him in.
一个秘密秘密组织？
A secret Secret Service?
是啊？它叫什么？
Yeah? What's it called?
它叫什么？
What's it called?
阿米蒂奇
Armitage.
一个秘密的秘密秘密组织叫阿米蒂奇？
A secret secret secret service called Armitage?
我们只向首相汇报
We answer only to the PM.
太不同凡响了 西蒙...
It's extraordinary, Simon...
的确是的
Indeed, it is.
...你以为我会
...That you'd think for one moment
被你这个垃圾胡扯给唬到吗？
that I would fall for such a steaming pile of old baloney.
干得好 塔克 不愧是每月之星
Well done, Tucker. You're not Spy of the Month for nothing.
- 谢谢 长官 - 这里让我来吧
- Thank you, sir. - Here, let me take that.
现在回家
Now go home.
- 什么？- 你才是胡扯
- What? - You're the one talking baloney.
你搞得一塌糊涂 孩子 现在离开吧
You're in way over your head, boy. Now run along.
不 我不走 长官 他在说谎
No! I won't go, sir. He's lying.
你太让我失望 让组织失望了
You've let me down, you've let the Service down
坦率地说 也让你自己失望
and, frankly, I think you've let yourself down.
- 但我... - 出去
- But I... - Now get out!
佩奇 库尔特曼 把自己的腿炸掉？
Patch Quartermain, of all people. Blowing his own legs off?
这才是深不可测
Now that's what I call deep cover.
我以前多么欣赏他
And to think how much I admired him.
他恨你
He hates you.
- 真的？- 一直都是
- Really? - He always has.
他认为你是个白痴 在军情7处没有立足之地
He thinks you're a moron with no place in MI7,
一个自大的初中无名小子
a jumped-up grammar school nobody
这就是为什么他想毁掉你
That's why he tried to destroy you.
现在 乔尼 就因为他毁了你
Now, Johnny, just because he ruined your life,
没有理由能阻止你手刃仇人 把他拿下
that's no reason for you to go rogue and take him down on your own.
但愿不会发生 我应该给你个更疯狂的想法
God forbid I should put a crazy idea like that in your head.
晚安 西蒙
Good night, Simon.
乔尼 把那个钥匙给我
Johnny, that key you showed me.
我用它把他绳之于法
We might need it to bring him in.
- 谢谢 - 不客气 先生
- Thank you. - You're welcome, sir.
白痴一个
Silly tit.
搞定
Bingo.
- 安排和我们的客户会面 - 当然
- Arrange a meeting with our client - Of course.
珀加索斯
Pegasus.
我们找到第三人了
We have the third man.
是乔尼·英格力士
It's Johnny English.
你好 佩奇
Hello, Patch.
寻求宽恕吗？
Looking for forgiveness?
这一切都结束了 英格力士 穷途末路了
It's all over for you now, English. It's the end of the line.
是啊 你很喜欢 是吧 佩奇？
Yes, you'd like that, wouldn't you, Patch?
毕竟 我只是个自大的初中无名小子而已 是吧？
After all, I'm just a jumped-up grammar school nobody, aren't I?
你说什么？
What are you talking about?
我知道你是旋风第三人
I know that you are the third man in Vortex.
没有 乔尼 你才是
No, Johnny. You are.
不 你是
No, you are.
No. You are!
所有探员 原地不动
Standby, all agents.
一切都到此为止
And it all ends here.
拿下他
Take him.
乔尼
Johnny.
嘿 看着点
Hey! Watch it!
找到他了 闪开 闪开
Got him! Move! Move!
不要让他跑了 快 快
Don't lose him. Go, go!
停下
Halt!
向西进入葡萄酒街 调动所有车辆
Heading west into Vine Street. Mobilise all vehicles.
傻瓜
Idiot!
不敢相信 你们居然跟丢了
You've lost him! I don't believe it.
嘿 你以为你是谁？
Oi! Who do you think you are?
抓住你了
Gotcha.
英格力士特工 停下 停下
Agent English, pull over! Pullover!
停下
Stop ii!
追上他
Get after him.
凯特 凯特 我不是旋风成员 我被诬陷了
Kate, Kate, I'm not Vortex. I've been framed.
你一定要相信我
You must believe me.
怎么搞定？
How will it be done?
和莫桑比克一样 一个人 单独工作
Same as in Mozambique. One person, apparently working alone.
谁来执行？
Who have you chosen?
这个问题我来搞定吧
Leave that with me.
苏黎世的帐户 说好的5亿美元
My account in Zurich. 500 million US dollars, as agreed.
你已经晕了几小时了
You've been out for hours
很幸运的只是皮肉伤
Well, you're lucky it was just a flesh wound.
现在 我今晚要去瑞士
Now, look, I'm going to Switzerland tonight,
在我走后 你可以呆这里
but you can stay here while I'm gone.
额 额 额 额
Mmm-hmm. Mmm-hmm.
我一直在看昌巴尔被杀当晚的录像
I've been going through the news footage from the night Chambal was killed.
有一些问题
And there's something not right.
昌巴尔先生被杀几秒后
Seconds after President Chambal was shot,
杀手就崩溃 然后死亡
the assassin collapses and dies.
尸检说是心脏衰竭
And the autopsy says heart failure.
如果你看监控录像的话...
But, if you go through the classified CCTV footage...
你没事吧？
You all right?
是啊 很好
Yeah, fine.
看看这个
Take a look at this.
暗杀前15分钟 他突然变狂躁
Fifteen minutes before the assassination, look, he's manic.
完全失去了控制
He's completely lost control of his body
突然之间 紧张
And then, suddenly, catatonic.
这里 等等
Here, wait.
有了
There.
有人和他说话
Someone was talking to him.
他完全不知道在做什么
I don't think he had any idea what he was doing.
旋风的秘密武器...
I think Vortex's secret weapon...
是一种精神控制药物
Is a mind control drug.
只有一种匹配这种症状
And only one fits the symptoms.
提姆莫... 提姆莫科斯林 芭比...
Timox... Timoxylin Bubby...
提姆莫科斯林 巴贝布特诺
Timoxeline Barbebutenol.
中情局10年前下令将其销毁
The CIA ordered its destruction 10 years ago.
而负责处理的是...
And the agent in charge of its disposal...
提图斯 费舍尔
Titus Fisher.
不知道该怎么谢你
I don't know how to thank you.
我喜欢外卖
I'd love a take-away.
可以考虑
Consider it done.
拉链没拉上
Flying low.
乔尼 关于旋风你该怎么办？
So, Johnny, what are you going to do about Vortex'?
不知道 如果西蒙在这就好了 他知道该怎么做
I don't know. If only Simon was here. He'd know what to do.
你为什么以为他比你更好？
Why do you think he's better than you?
他是神
Well, the man's a god.
我喜欢凡人
Well, I prefer mortals.
纯净的 复杂的 令人发狂的凡人
Pure, complicated, maddening mortals.
我才认识到什么真正令我兴奋
I've come to realise that what's really exciting to me
是伟大的忠诚 决心和勇气
is great loyalty, determination, and courage.
你在临床上一直让我着迷
You have always fascinated me, clinically.
但现在你...
But now you...
萨姆纳女士 你的瞳孔在扩张
Ms Sumner, your pupils are dilating.
是吗？
Are they?
脸颊发红
Your cheeks are colouring.
眼睛接触加深
Eye contact deepening.
心跳速度上升
Heart-rate rising.
萨姆纳女士 我们正在泄漏情绪
Ms Sumner, I believe we're emotionally leaking.
- 去卧室 快 - 没问题
- The bedroom, quickly. - Absolutely.
现在
Now!
- 是谁？- 你好
- Hello? - Hello.
- 哦 西蒙 - 嗨 凯特
- Oh, Simon. - Hi, Kate.
准备好了吗？我开车送你去机场
You ready? I'll drive you to the airport.
太好了 我拿下包
How nice. I'll just get my bag.
就你一个人吗？
You alone?
- 当然
- No. - Of course.
一直在工作？
Been working?
一直在观察中国首相 你呢？
Been brushing up on the Chinese PM. You?
正努力跟踪小丑乔尼·英格力士
We're trying to track clown Johnny English
关于旋风有一些问题要问他
There's some questions we want to ask him, about Vortex.
你见过他吗？
I don't suppose you've seen him, have you?
没有
No.
没有藏着他？
Not hiding him away?
不是我喜欢的类型 走吧？
Not my type. Shall we?
恩 恩
Mmm-hmm.
安布罗斯
Ambrose.
有个亚当斯先生要见你 科林
There's a Mr Adams to see you, Colin.
- 您好 塔克 - 你在这做什么？
- Hello, Tucker. - What are you doing here?
全国所有特工都在抓你
Every agent in the country is after you.
关于安布罗斯是对的
We were right about Ambrose
"我们"？
What do you mean "we"?
如果我们能够迅速采取行动 还可以...
And if we can act fast, we can still...
谁叫你不听 对吧？
You wouldn't listen, would you?
你以为什么都知道 其实不是
You think you know it all. Well' you don't!
特工是我的全部
Being an agent means everything to me.
谢谢你 我被停职了
And, thanks to you, I'm suspended!
你们要橘子汽水吗？
Would you boys like some orange squash?
- 不 谢谢 - 再见 谢谢 妈妈
- No, thank you. - Bye, thanks, Mum.
塔克 安布罗斯在瑞士 我们要赶紧了
Tucker, Ambrose is in Switzerland. We are in Tooting.
我回来是因为国家需要我
I am here because my country needs me.
也需要你
And because it needs you, too.
- 劳斯莱斯 - 就绪 长官
- Royce. - Ready, sir.
走吧
Come.
前方有障碍物
Obstruction detected.
导航到瑞士 干死某人
Set the sat nav for Switzerland Let's kick some bottom.
您已到达目的地
You have arrived at your destination.
祝你好运 长官
Good luck, sir!
乐堡垒 上下一条路
Le Bastion. One way up, one way down.
来吧 看我们的装备
Come on. Let's get the stuff.
哇 看 T-2地对空导弹
Whoa, look. The T-2 ground-to-air missile!
那是个D-7防弹盾
That's a D-7 bulletproof shield.
相信我 塔克
Take it from me, Tucker.
你还在穿开裆裤时 我就玩过它们了
I was working with these while you were stringing conkers.
P-8的格斗钩？
The P-8 grapple hook?
测试
Check.
- 预计高度？- 三十五英尺
- Estimated height? - Thirty-five feet.
看你的了 塔克
All yours, Tucker.
长官 我能说句...？
Can I just say, sir'?
太酷了
This is just great.
好了 继续
Well, go on.
D-16升降器 我们上
The D-16 ascender, and up we go.
您确定是升降器吗 长官？
Are you sure that's the ascender, sir?
对 没错 我对它太熟了
Yes, yes, I'd know it anywhere.
特工遇险 特工遇险
Agent in distress. Agent in distress.
我在这里
I am over here!
闭嘴 闭嘴
Shut up! Shut up!
我在这里
I am over here!
激活视觉定位
Activating visual locator.
三 二 一
Three, two, one.
4区又入侵者
Intruders in Sector Four!
天呐 不要让我死在瑞士人手中
Dear God, let me not die at the hands of the Swiss.
塔克 你来攻击我
Tucker, now listen. I want you to attack me
- 什么？- 经过一番打斗
- What? - After a struggle,
你可以"逮捕我" 把我作为你的俘虏带进去
you can "arrest me" and take me inside as your prisoner.
- 长官 我不能 - 塔克 这是命令
- Sir, I can't. - Tucker, that's an order.
打我 打我
Hit me. Hit me.
来吧 用力点
Come on, harder.
- 很好吧 长官？- 是的 好多了
- Better, sh'? - Yes, much better.
我知道为什么大家喜欢这了
I can see how people get a taste for this.
我有一个更好的主意 开枪射你
I got a better idea. I'll shoot you!
不 不 不要
No, no, no.
- 去死吧 旋风败类 - 塔克
- Die, Vortex scum! - Tucker!
塔克特工
Agent Tucker!
是乔尼·英格力士
It's Johnny English.
打包他
Bag him.
这玻璃可以承受迫击炮的袭击
The glass can withstand mortar attack.
门是单向的 可以出去 但没人能进来
The door's one-way. You can get out, but no one gets in.
太好了
Excellent.
准备好了吗 斯莱特？
You ready, Slater'?
你准备好后
I'll have them send refreshments to your room
我让他们送点心到你房间 珀加索斯
when you're ready, Pegasus.
谢谢 1号特工
Thank you, Agent One.
这里开始我来吧 同志们
I'll take it from here, boys.
别动
Hold it right there!
出示你的身份证
Let me see your ID.
- 对不起 - 什么...
- Excuse me - What the...
住手
Stop!
警告 这是个指定的冲突区
Warning, this is a designated conflict zone.
长官？长官？
Sir'? Sir?
- 非常感谢 - 不客气 珀加索斯
- Thank you so much - You're welcome, Pegasus.
珀加索斯
Pegasus.
喝下去 喝下去
Go on. Go on.
那是什么鬼东西？
What the hell is that?
长官？长官？
Sir'? Sir?
- 英格力士 - 珀加索斯
- English! - Pegasus.
他们要让你杀向平
They're going to make you kill Xiang Ping!
你疯了
You're insane!
1号特工 感谢上帝
Agent One, thank God.
他不会帮你 他是旋风第三人
He won't help you. He's the third member of Vortex.
是吧 西蒙？
Aren't you, Simon?
他给你些提姆莫科斯林 芭比...
Here to give you some Timoxy bubby...
提姆莫斯 芭比
Timoxy bubby
提姆莫斯 芭比...
Timoxy bubby...
他给你用一种药物 让你服从他的命令
To give you a drug that will make you obey his every command.
西蒙 我很感兴趣
I'm intrigued, Simon.
你要怎么用呢？
How exactly were you going to administer it?
注射？
By injection?
通过通风口排放某种气体？
Some hideous gas through the air vents?
或参在饮料里？
Or by spiking her drink?
提姆莫科斯林 巴贝布特诺
Timoxeline Barbebutenol.
他会在任何时刻进入狂躁阶段
He'll enter the manic phase any moment now.
我警告你 我一直在训练抵制这种东西
I have to warn you that I've been trained to resist this kind of thing.
你这卑鄙家伙
You swine.
1号特工 这是怎么回事？
Agent One, what's going on?
在这个阶段 他相当无害
He's quite harmless at this phase.
这种药物会杀了他 但之前
The drug will kill him, but just before it does,
会有一个简短时刻 我让他做啥 他就会做啥
there'll be a short window where he'll do everything I tell him to.
可怜的乔尼
Poor Johnny.
你从来没有真正进入军情7处 乔尼
You were never really Ml-7, Johnny.
你永远不会成为我们中一员
You were never really one of us.
现在 你即将成为最有名的特工
Now you're about to become our most famous agent.
你会完全照我说的做
You'll now do exactly as I tell you.
你是特勤局和国家的叛徒
You are a traitor to the Service and to your country.
让她闭嘴 老伙计
Shut her up, old chap.
- 鸭 - 什么？
- Duck. - What?
我警告过你
I warned you.
好吧 斯莱特 让他准备好
Okay, Slater. Let's get him ready.
准备就绪
Ready.
平总理 很高兴终于见到你
Premier Ping, it's a pleasure to finally meet you.
旅途愉快吧？
You had a pleasant flight, I trust?
我刚问总理他的旅途愉快吗？
I was just asking the Premier if he had a pleasant flight.
凯特 乔尼回队了
Kate, Johnny's back on the team.
什么？
What?
仔细检查过了 首相和中国总理都批准了
It's all checked out and the PM and the Chinese have approved it.
- 批准什么？- 他代替潘梅拉
- Approved what? - He's standing in for Pamela.
是不是很棒？
Isn't it great?
对不起 塔克特工
Excuse me. Agent Tucker.
很好 很好 你的妻子呢？
Good, good. And your wife is well?
锁上 乔尼
Lock it up, Johnny.
太好了
Wonderful.
That's it.
总理 我很感谢你在这个时候同意见面
Premier, I am most grateful you have agreed to meet me at this time.
这是我们的荣幸
It is our pleasure.
首相 保持这个基调
Maintain that tone, Prime Minister.
避免对视 保持目光接触
Avoid confrontation, keep eye contact.
我可以告诉你 中国人民
I can assure you that the Chinese people
一直认为英国人是非常可怕的
have always regarded the British people as completely horrible.
- 可敬 - 可敬
- Honourable. - Honourable.
非常可敬
Completely honourable.
当然
Of course.
我非常想...
I was very keen to meet...
乔尼 站起来 去放水的桌子
Johnny, stand up and go to the water table.
首相 如果我们迅速采取行动的话
Premier, I believe the present danger
我认为目前的危险是可避免的
can be averted if we act swiftly.
伸进你的右口袋
Go to your right pocket.
我们为珀加索斯设计的
We designed it for Pegasus.
嗯 现在太晚了
Well, it's too bloody late now.
自然点
Just act natural.
- 首相 习惯上... - 有点不对劲
- Prime Minister, traditionally... - Somethings wrong.
中方不建议...
...China does not respond well to advice...
拔出口红
Pull out the barrel.
现在 乔尼 我让你杀向平
Now, Johnny, I want you to kill Xiang Ping.
哦 神哪 不要
Oh, dear God, no.
他被控制了
He's being controlled.
被谁？
By who?
安布罗斯
Ambrose.
杀死向平
Shoot Xiang Ping!
意志主宰身体
Mind must be master of the body.
他在抵制它
He's resisting it.
他的左手打右手
His left hand is fighting the right hand.
来吧 乔尼
Come on, Johnny.
如果我能中断发射频率
If I can interrupt the frequency,
我可以组织安布罗斯与他沟通
I could stop Ambrose from communicating with him.
英格力士 站起来
English, stand up!
来吧 来吧
Come on. Come on.
长官 他将在50秒内死亡
He'll be dead in 50 seconds, sir.
塔克
Tucker!
来吧
Come on.
- 扣动扳机 - 我侵入了
- Pull the trigger! - I'm in.
听我说 这是西蒙 安布罗斯
Listen to me, this is Simon Ambrose,
我命令你杀死向平
and I order you to shoot Xiang Ping!
十秒钟 长官
Ten seconds, sir.
开枪
Fire!
走 走 走
Go, go, go.
该离开这了
Time to get out of here.
不要开枪
Hold your fire!
退下
Stand down!
他的脉搏在下降
His pulse is dropping.
不能让他死
Don't lose him!
加油 长官
Come on, sir.
打开你的思维 英格力士 你可以重生
Open your head, English, and you shall be reborn.
快到了
Almost there.
谢谢 凯特
Thank you, Kate.
我只是路过
I was passing.
长官
Sir.
塔克
Tucker!
欢迎回来 长官
Welcome back, sir.
谢谢 塔克
Thank you, Tucker.
如果你不介意 我不吻你
I won't kiss you, if you don't mind.
好了 无所谓
Well, whatever.
安布罗斯在哪？
Where's Ambrose?
英格力士？
English?
长官 你在做什么 长官？
Sir. What are you doing, sir'?
特工指南第17章第5条 永远不要质疑高级特工
Guideline 17-5: Never question a senior agent in the field.
不要
No!
安布罗斯 你这个五星级垃圾
Ambrose' you five-star turd.
很牛逼啊 乔尼
Another balls-up, Johnny.
哦
Ooh.
你有什么毛病啊？
What's the matter with you?
一切都结束了 安布罗斯
It's all over, Ambrose.
你可以出卖你的国家 欺骗你的朋友
You can betray your country, you can cheat your friends,
但你无法从乔尼英格力士...
but you can't get away from Johnny English...
再见了 乔尼
So long, Johnny!
D-7
The D-7.
防弹盾牌
The bulletproof shield!
嘿 不管用
Hey! It's not working!
它是T-2 长官
It's the T-2, sir!
- 他... 哦 他还活着 - 那是T-2
- Is he... Oh, he's alive! - It's the T-2!
关上它 关上它
Close it. Close ii!
没用的东西
Stupid thing!
噢 乔尼
Oh, Johnny.
T-2
The T-2.
塔克 聪明的孩子
Tucker, you clever boy.
我无比高兴
I couldn't be more delighted.
旋风的幕后主使人已被逮捕
Vortex's paymasters have been arrested,
中国政府感谢英国和特勤部门
and China has expressed its gratitude to both Britain and the Service.
我们欠英格力士很多
We owe English a great deal.
恢复他的爵位是个很好的决策
Well, reinstating his knighthood is a truly lovely gesture.
对他来说就像给了他全世界
And it will mean the world to him.
女皇陛下 马上过来
Her Majesty will be with him shortly.
抓到你了 抓到你了
Gotcha! Gotcha.
抓到你了
Got you!
受够了 你这个老巫婆
Just about had enough of you, you old cow!
你无处可逃了 珀加索斯
You're going nowhere! Pegasus!
英格力士
English!
就是她 杀手清洁工 我终于抓到她了
It's her! It's the killer cleaner! Finally, I've got her!
你永远不知道什么时候死 对吧？
You never know when it's over, do you?
过来 过来 过来 过来
Well, it's over, over, over, over, over!
我不知道该怎么感谢你
I don't know how to thank you.
我喜欢外卖
I'd love a take-away.
可以考虑
Consider it done.